

#### Contacts

Dnipro,Ukraine

+380974335970

rudomanovdmitrij@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/ https://github.com/

#### **Tech Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- 0000
- SCSSGIT
- JavaScript
- WebPack
- \_
- React
- ReduxVue
- Node

## Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Decision-making
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Stress management

## **Language Skills**

- Russian : Native
- Ukrainian : Native
- English : Upper-intermediate

#### **Front-End Developer**

# **Dmitrij Rudomanov**

I'm a Frontend developer with experience in building websites and APP`s. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store – I can help! I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, SCSS, JS, React, Vue, Node. Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!

## **Project Experience**

1.	DARK NOTES   Project Link
	React-TypeScript project.Simple and usefull Notes App
2.	WALLET   Project Link
	Team React-NodeJS project.Simple and usefull Wallet App
3.	PHONEBOOK   Project Link
	Solo React-Redux project.Simple user friendly Pnonebook App
4.	SHOP   Project Link
	Solo Vue project.Online shop with currency exchange
5.	FILMOTEKA   Project Link [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
	JS team project with me as Teamlead. Movie site easy to use
6.	WEBSTUDIO   Project Link [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS ]
	Educational markup project. Simple and Interactive
7.	ICECREAM   Project Link
	Team project.lceCream selling web-site.Role:Developer,Code reviewer
8.	WOODER   Project Link HTML5, CSS3, SCSS ]
	Building an interesting landing website for wood furniture company
9.	OFDR   Project Link
	Web-site for insurance companie.
LO.	FUNIRO   Project Link
	A modern web-store that sels best quality furniture
L1.	LOGO   Project Link
	Website for online Sport-shop
L2.	BENTLEY   Project Link
	Working on official Bentley web-page in Ukraine
L3.	LUX-TRADER   Project Link
	Luxury Auctions Web-site with golden design.
L4.	BINARY   Project Link
	Modern innovative designers web-page

15. PRIME-ONE | Project Link ...... [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]

Web-Site for very creative foodmaking organiztion

#### **Work Experience**

### **Svet-LED Company Web-site editor**

September 2019 - January 2019 | Ukraine

- Editing the list of products on the site
- Products information update

#### Restaurant 'SHO PO CHEM'

#### Waiter

June 2019 - September 2019 | Ukraine

- Taking orders from visitors
- Customer service

#### **Education**

#### PSACEA

International Economics and business

September 2018 - June 2023 | Ukraine

## **Additional Education**

GOIT